Mojo mojo mojospy
This world is bursting with color
Truth and lies deceive our eyes
Look closely with your heart
You'll find the truth is not far away
Hey! you good or bad?!
Truth and lies
Can't escape this heart's keen eye
Take all your courage
Maybe you can save this world
Mojo mojo mojospy
Mojospy
Tuna Town
An evil organization led by Lord Eye
The Illumin-Eye's plan to summon a flood was foiled
Two key members of The Illumin-Eye
Mr.K and Shaker
are missing
One year later
The darkness seemed to have completely faded
But evil never stops
Episode 1: The Carnival Terror Attack, Part 1
Stop!
Don't run!
Tomorrow night
at Tuna Town's annual
New Year float parade celebration,
the mayor will present, on behalf of the town,
the honorary citizen's Keys of Hope
to the heroes who, one year ago,
saved the town.
Heroes
Doesn't that include me too?
Stop!
Who's there? So noisy!
Damn kid!
Let us teach you a lesson!
Heads up, old man!
Who do you think would believe you?
Super—cute angel Jingjing
Super—pet servant Chickenix
A mind so brilliant it's explosive,
Instincts so sharp it's terrifying
I, soon-to-be world-famous detective
Locky, accuse
the mastermind of kidnapping a pet chinchilla
and blackmailing wealthy Fuldo.
It's you!
Jingjing!
Chickenix!
Yes.
Good Juice Super-Sticky Sugar Fruit Juice is here!
For the good of the people
They'd better surrender to me right now!
Super—Justice Officer Inspector Sima
Hello, Inspector Sima!
Hello, Jingjing.
Oh, right.
Where's Locky?
Jingjing! Jingjing! Let me out!
The juice glued the box shut!
Super—
Zero-Popularity Male Lead, Locky
Super—handsome
And that's the end of the character introductions.
Uh, okay, okay.
Professor Gui
How's the deciphering of the ancient book's text coming along?
Mr. Jimmy Chen
According to the copy of the Illumin Ancient Book you sent over
This ancient script is somewhat similar to the writing our country recently
collected from the crystal ice coffin.
This writing must be from
before the birth of modern civilization—
a script from a very ancient civilization.
Professor Yin, what do you think?
Cracking ancient scripts requires two conditions.
One is sufficient textual material.
The other is that with known scripts
connections can be established.
Based on the earlier Tuna Town
tsunami incident,
I've already found that on certain pages
characters are directly tied to rituals,
and to records of rain.
I believe once the material is further refined,
fully deciphering this ancient book will be no problem.
Oh, right.
I have another new discovery.
Detective Chen, this is—
this is what I found when I adopted
Locky, in the bamboo basket—
two torn pages.
After Lord Eye's failure,
the Ancient Book of Light he took away
was actually incomplete.
I'm faxing it to you.
Maybe it can help us uncover
the true secret of The Illumin-Eye
Okay.
I'll compile a set of
materials on ruins worldwide where the Eye symbol was found
and enter them all into the database.
Also,
About Locky's origins
Can you provide some more detailed information?
No problem.
Lately, his Hair Horns
have started acting up again.
Detective Chen,
Could Locky
be from the Ancient Kingdom of Light?
Uncle! Uncle!
Uh-oh.
Uncle
Uncle, wake up!
We need to get ready
for Tuna Town's
first anniversary reconstruction celebration.
A huge crowd of fans is waiting for my autograph.
Autograph~
A mind so brilliant it's explosive
Instincts so sharp it's terrifying
I'm the world-famous detective
Locky
Why are you trying to be some famous detective?
What about Conen?
What is Conen?
This is my idol
Sholmes's classic pose
All right, all right
Locky
You two go get my wallet
There are a few toy store gift vouchers in it
Really?
Bye, Uncle
Wait, that's not right
When did he find out
where my wallet is?
Hello?
Officer Han
Jimmy
Are you free today?
Come with me to check out
the flowers decorating the scenic area's parade float
Sure
Mr.K is so cute
Why am I not there?
Little one
Are you looking for a toy that looks like you?
Over there.
Darn it!
Do you remember, one year ago
the day Tuna Town was nearly destroyed by Storm and a tsunami?
Because of him
And him, and him, and him
our home was finally safe and sound.
Tomorrow night
after the festival's main float parade
at the town square
the town key will be awarded
the Keys of Hope
to the great international detective Jimmy Chen
and genius teen detective Hawxing
and the police world's oddballs
Han Jiawei, Inspector Sima
Why?
Why am I not in any of the reports?
Does nobody like me?
Locky.
Locky, don't cry.
Locky is Jingjing's savior
Jingjing likes Locky!
Damn it!
I'm gonna find my uncle and get some answers
Jimmy
Look
This flower is so pretty
Yeah
This rose smells so good
Hmph, that's obviously a climbing rose
Flower lovers
are really getting fewer and fewer
Officer Han
The flowers used for the police station's parade float
give them back
No, no, no!
Sorry, sorry!
It's my fault
Mr. Flower
Why is this soil red?
Flowers are born from the soil's nourishment
Coral Reef Garden's soil
is a special aluminum-rich soil
It can give flowers
the best nutrients
Oh, what a shame.
Good soil like this is hard to come by.
Mr. Flower,
The soil here is different from over there, isn't it?
I host tea parties here regularly.
I invite fellow nature lovers
to gather together.
That soil from over there
was brought by one of the kids.
Let me test how well it works.
But this soil really is something.
The flowers are blooming happily too.
Mr. Flower,
Do you remember that person's name
and contact info?
I'd also like to try
asking for some soil to grow flowers.
What was that person called again?
Oh dear, I'm getting old.
Oh right, her name's Do—
Do... what was it?
Dorothy?
Yes, yes, yes!
How do you know that?
Don't tell me...
Oh right, he also said—
If anyone asks about him
Just hand something to that person.
Hold on!
Dear viewers,
The celebration is in two days.
But something's wrong with the sculpture in the square.
Hahaha, this kid
A naughty little kid wreaks havoc
Locky?!
Tomorrow's celebration will likely be affected.
Unable to proceed normally
Locky
Got into trouble again.
Jimmy
Look.
On this night of celebration, The Illumin-Eye will send you a "blazing" gift! ——Avenger Dorothy
The Illumin-Eye
I really don't want to.
All alone, so lonely.
But life...
There are bound to be some unhappy times.
Goodbye to Today
Always leaves people feeling disappointed.
Let's see tomorrow.
The horizon is beckoning to me
Every day as the sun rises and sets
Seize the time to dream up more
Look forward to every second, every moment in life
Bright eyes are sparkling
A smile facing the sunlight
Bravely speak out that little feeling treasured in your heart
A morning breeze blows gently in your face
It carries away wishes from all these years
It will quietly be planted at the crossing of growing up